Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Robert J. Levine papers
1953-2014
MS 1889
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
78.81
(98 boxes)
The collection comprises correspondence; office, professional, and related topical files; course materials for medical ethics classes; and editorial files for IRB: A Journal of Human Subjects Research, documenting the career of Robert J. Levine as doctor, professor, author, and leader in the field of medical ethics, specializing in research using human subjects.
Levine, Robert J.
Conditions Governing Access
The bulk of the papers are open for research. Accession 2016-M-0064 is restricted until 2089 as established by Yale Corporation regulations http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa/collections/research-use-of-yale-university-archives.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository.
Biographical / Historical
Robert J. Levine was born in Wantagh, New York, on December 29, 1934. He graduated from Duke University, North Carolina, in 1954, and earned his M.D. from George Washington University School of Medicine, Washington, DC, in 1958. He was a surgeon with the United States Public Health Service, 1960-1964, and held numerous positions at Yale University School of Medicine including: assistant professor of Medicine and Pharmacology, 1965-1968, chief of the Section of Clinical Pharmacology, 1966-1974; associate professor of Medicine and Pharmacology, 1968-1973; director of the Physicians Associate Program, 1973-1975; chair of the Institutional Review Board at Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1969-2000; director of the Center for Interdisciplinary Research on AIDS, Law, Policy and Ethics Core; and co-director of the Interdisciplinary Center for Bioethics, 2005-2007. Levine was the founding editor of IRB: A Review of Human Subjects Research and has authored numerous publications, including Ethics and Regulation of Clinical Research.
Scope and Contents
The collection comprises correspondence; office, professional, and related topical files; course materials for medical ethics classes; and editorial files for IRB: A Journal of Human Subjects Research, documenting the career of Robert J. Levine as doctor, professor, author, and well-known leader in the field of medical ethics, specializing in research using human subjects.
Although arranged in series, there is considerable overlap of materials between series. For example, Topical Files may also contain correspondence and reports.
Arrangement
The papers are arranged in six series and two additions: I. Correspondence, 1953-1997. II. Office Files, 1962-1997. III. Medical Ethics Course Materials, 1978-1996. IV. Editorial Files for IRB: A Journal of Human Subjects Research, 1976-1996. V. Professional Files, 1972-2002. VI. Topical Files, 1958-2000.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Robert J. Levine, 2007, 2008, and 2016.
Medical ethics; Levine, Robert J.; Council for International Organizations of Medical Sciences
- Correspondence, 1953-1997; Series I
  Arrangement
  Folders of correspondence are arranged alphabetically by correspondents' last name, organization name, or journal title. There is also one small run of correspondence arranged chronologically. The original order of folders has been maintained.
  Scope and Contents
  This series comprises incoming and outgoing correspondence of both a professional and personal nature.
  - Abboud, Frank, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Abod, Jennifer, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abrams, Ellen, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abramson, Norman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acheson, George, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acheson, Roy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ackerman, Sigurd, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Albert, Lee, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allen, David, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alleyne, Gao, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alper, Milton, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alpert, Ann, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Journal of Medical Science, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Susan, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Andrew, Barbara, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annenberg Center, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arctander, Rosemary, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Arkansas, University of, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Aronson, David, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Asher, Linda, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Azarnoff, Daniel, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bach, Peter H., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bachand, Romeo, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Baker, Sidney, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Balaban, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Balint, John A., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ball, Michael, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ballard, Ann, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Barchas, Jack, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Barclay, William, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bardhan, K. D., 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Basson, Marc D., 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Batson, Blair, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Baue, Arthur, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Baumgartner, Leona, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Baumrind, Diana, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bean, William B., 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Beaven, Michael, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Beck, William C., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Beck, William T., 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Beecher, Henry K., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Beernink, Margaret, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bellwin, Alexander, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Berger, Alex, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Berger, Harvey, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bernanke, Max, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bernat, James, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bernheim, J. L., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bertelli, Aldo, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Besunder, Rhonda, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bigelow, Llewellyn, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Birtel, Frank, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Blanpied, William A., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bloom, Floyd, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Blumstein, James F., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Bogdonoff, Morton, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Bogomolny, Robert, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Bonkowski, Herbert, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bonnet, Philip D., 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Bonta, Ivan, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bouhuys, Arend, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bower, B. F., 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bransome, Edwin D., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Branson, Roy, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Brashear, Richard, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Brathovde, James, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Brigat-Asare, Peter, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Brodie, Bernard B., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Brodny, M. Leopold, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Brook, Robert, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Brooks, Frank, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Broseghini, Albert L., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Brown, Michael, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Brown, Thomas, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Brunjes, Shannon, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Buckingham, Robert, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Buehler, David, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bullock, Ward, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Burck, Russell, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Burgower, William, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Burkhalter, Alan, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Burkholder, Ann, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Burrow, Gerald N., 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Buyske, D. A., 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Caldwell, Grace, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Callahan, John, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Cannon, David, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Caplan, Robert, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Caraley, Demetrios, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Carlock, Stan, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Carter, Charles E. (Nick), 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Case, David, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Cavander, Sasha, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Celestin, L. R., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Chadwick, David, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Chalkley, Donald, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Challoner, David, 1971-1978 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Chan, Carlyle, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Chapple, Paul J., 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Chavez-Pardo, Rodolfo, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Chayet, Neil L., 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Check, William, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Chedd, Graham, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Chen, Michael, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Chernin, Eli, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Chidsey, Charles A., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Christian, Carin, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Clark, Frederick A., Jr., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Clark, Janet L., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Clark, Mervin, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Clark, William G., 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Clarke, Cheryl, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Cleveland, Joseph, Circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Cline, Martin J., 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Cohart, Edward, 1973, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Cohen, Eva, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Cohen, Martin, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Cohen, Phin, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Cole, Belle, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Cole, Jack W., 1973, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Coleman, Bernard S., 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Columbia University, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Comer, James, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Committee of a Thousand for Better Health Regulations, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Condemi, John J., 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Conn, Howard F., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Connor, William, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Constantopoulos, G., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Cook, Charles D., 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Cooper, John A. D., 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Cooper, Theodore, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Coraluzzo, Kay, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Costa, Erminio, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Cote, John, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Cowan, Dale H., 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Cowett, Richard, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Cox, J. Randolph, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Crabbé, Jean, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Cranefield, Paul, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Crelin, Edmund, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Criley, J. Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Crossman, Shepherd R., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Crout, J. Richard, 1966-1972 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Crowley, Francis L., 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Cruickshank, Alexander, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Curry, Jerome, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Cushing, Maureen, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Danbury Hospital, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Danon, Abraham, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - D'Aprix, John, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Data, Joann, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Davis, Carol, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Davis, Richard E., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Day, Jack, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Day, Mel, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Dayton, Seymour, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Debnath, Asok, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - De Carville, John, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Decker, Ed, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Decker, Marcel, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Defabaugh, Gretchen L., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - De Fronzo, Ralph A., 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 164-165)
  - DeLellis, Ronald, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Delmar, Diana, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - DeLorenzo, Robert J., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - DeLuca, Vincent A., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Di Bona, Gerald, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Didier, E. Paul, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Dieck, Gretchen, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Dietschy, John, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - DiPalma, Joseph, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Dobbins, William O., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Dolovich, Jerry, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Done, Alan, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Doudera, Edward, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Additional material, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Drug Therapy, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Duane, Therese, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Dubrasquet, Marcelle, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Dubroff, Jerome, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Duff, Ray, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Duffie, Edward, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Dunbar, Jacqueline M., 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Duncan, Catherine, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Duncan, Roy, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Dunea, George, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Dunnigan, Jacques, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Dusseau, John, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Duval, Benjamin, Undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Dwyer, John, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Eaton, David, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Eberlein, Kimberley, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Edelman, Norman, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Eisner, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Elliott, Henry, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Ellison, Edwin H., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Emmerglick, Leonard J., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - Emmert, Wil, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Engel, Ronald L., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Erdös, Ervin, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - Escovitz, Gerald, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - Euromed, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - Evans, Hilary, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - Evans, Lorenzo, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - Ewell, John W., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - Ewing, Jay, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Fabro, J. Alfred, 1970-1983 (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Fantarella, Laura, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - Farb, Mark, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - Farb, Thomas F., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - Farmer, Douglas, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Farnsworth, Dana, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - Farrar, John T., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - Feingold, David, 1971, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - Felarca, Lourdes, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - Ferguson, Roger, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - Fillmore, Mary, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - Finch, Stuart C., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - Finkelstein, Fredric, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - Fischer, Carl, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - Fish, Barbara, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - Fishbein, Estelle A., 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - Fisher, Lloyd D., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - Fisher, Seymour, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - FitzSimons, Louise, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - Fliedner, Theodor, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - Foraker, Alvan, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 230)
  - Forman, Lesley Nan, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Foundations Fund for Research in Psychiatry, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - Frank, Reuben, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 233)
  - Franklin, Cory, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 234)
  - Franklin, William, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 235)
  - Frazier, Kendrick, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 236)
  - Frazier, William, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 237)
  - Frederickson, Donald, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 238)
  - Freeland, A. Jerome, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 239)
  - Freireich, Emil, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 240)
  - Frias, Jaime, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 241)
  - Friedell, Gilbert, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 242)
  - Friedman, Steven, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 243)
  - Fruthaler, G. J., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 244)
  - Fudenberg, H. Hugh, 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 245)
  - Furman, Robert, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 246)
  - Furrow, Barry, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 247)
  - Gallant, Donald, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Galveston, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Gardner, Frank, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Gardner, Karen, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Garrity, Jim, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Gass, Ronald, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Geballe, Shelley, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Geertsma, Mary Ann, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Gehan, Edmund, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Gellhorn, Alfred, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - George Washington University, 1953-1971 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Gershkoff, Arthur, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Gersoff, Wayne, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Gerstenhaber, Brett, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Getsiv, Ludmilla, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Ghio, Joan, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Giertz, Gustav, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Gilbert, David, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Gillespie, Elizabeth, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Gillioppe, Benjamin W., Circa 1972 (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Gilmer, Sam O., Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Gimenes, M. Gloria G., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Glaser, Rich, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Glass, Robert, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Glazer, William M., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Gleicher, Lisa, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Glitz, William, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Goldberg, Harold, Undated (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Goldsmith, Carl, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - Goldstein, Steven, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - Goodman, Ira, 1974, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - Goodman, Louis S., 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - Gordon, Jeffrey, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Gortner, Susan, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - Goth, Andres, 1970, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Gralla, Edward, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - Granoff, Morris, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - Greaves, Malcolm W., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - Greco, Ralph, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - Green, Jack P., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - Green, Nicholas, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - Green, Patricia, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Greenbaum, Lowell, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Greenblatt, David, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - Greengard, Paul, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  - Greenwald, Robert P., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Grench, Charles, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Greep, Nancy, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Griener, Glenn, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - Griffis, Judy, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Grosshandler, Stanley, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Grossman, Morton I., 1966-1975 (Box 3, Folder 299)
  - Grune & Stratton, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 300)
  - Guevara, Carlos, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 301)
  - Gyorffy, Pilar, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 302)
  - Hackett, Thomas, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 303)
  - Hailman, H. F., 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 304)
  - Häkanson, Rolf, 1965-1974 (Box 3, Folder 305)
  - Halberstam, Michael J., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 306)
  - Hall, Thomas, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 307)
  - Hallam, Kris, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 308)
  - Halliday, William, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 309)
  - Halprin, Kenneth, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 310)
  - Halstead, Linda, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 311)
  - Hamilton, Bruce, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 312)
  - Hammarsten, James F., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 313)
  - Hardman, Harold, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - Harford, Robert, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 315)
  - Hargest, Thomas, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 316)
  - Harris, Louis, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 317)
  - Harrison, Donald C., 1966-1980 (Box 3, Folder 318)
  - Hartford, James, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 319)
  - Hartmann, William, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 320)
  - Haseltine, Florence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 321)
  - Hausman, Michael, 1978, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 322)
  - Hawes, Catherine, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 323)
  - Hayes, Kay, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 324)
  - Hedberg, Phyllis, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 325)
  - Heisler, Seymour (thesis), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 326)
  - Helminski, Frank, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 327)
  - Herrera, Nilo, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 328)
  - Herron, Earl, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 329)
  - Hersh, Theodore, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 330)
  - Hershman, Jerome, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 331)
  - Hess, Sid, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 332)
  - Hewitt, H. G., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 333)
  - Higgins, James, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 334)
  - Higgins, June, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 335)
  - Hilderley, Laura J., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 336)
  - Hittelman, Karl J., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 337)
  - Hoffman, Joseph, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 338)
  - Hoffman, Roger, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 339)
  - Hoffman, William P., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 340)
  - Hoffmann, Fred, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 341)
  - Hogan, Thomas W., 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 342)
  - Hogue, Carol, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 343)
  - Hollingsworth, J. W., 1972, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 344)
  - Holly, Marcia, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 345)
  - Holman, Halstead, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 346)
  - Holt, Peter, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 347)
  - Hon, Edward, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 348)
  - Honig, Howard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 349)
  - Hopper, Linnea, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 350)
  - Horovitz, Zola, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 351)
  - Hoyer, Leon, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 352)
  - Hsia, Y. Edward (Ted), 1970-1977 (Box 3, Folder 353)
  - Huffman, David, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 354)
  - Hull, Alison, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 355)
  - Hutcheon, Duncan, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 356)
  - Hyde, Richard, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 357)
  - Import, Robin, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 358)
  - International Medicine News Group, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 359)
  - Isay, Jane, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 360)
  - Itoh, Zen, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 361)
  - Jacobsen, Janice, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 362)
  - Jacobson, David, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 363)
  - Jakubowski, Ann, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 364)
  - Jerzy Glass, George B., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 365)
  - Jones, Thomas R., 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 367)
  - Josephson, Alan, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 368)
  - Kamm, Arthur, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 369)
  - Kaplan, Louis, 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 370)
    - Jewett, John, III, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 366)
  - Kapp, Daniel, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 371)
  - Karzon, David, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 372)
  - Katz, Leonard, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 373)
  - Kaufman, Paul, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 374)
  - Kavanagh, Lloyd, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 375)
  - Kay, Calum, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 376)
  - Keaney, N. P., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 377)
  - Keating, Trudy, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 378)
  - Kellen, J. A., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 379)
  - Kellner, Patty, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 380)
  - Keystone Meeting, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - Kimmel, Allan J., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - King, Jackson T., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Kiskaddon, Sarah H., 1996 October-1997 January (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Klainer, Lawrence, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - Kleiman, Terry, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - Klein, Donald, 1979, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - Kliger, Alan S., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Klinge, Valerie, Undated (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - Kneedler, Julia, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Kneten, Norval, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Kobayashi, Yutaka, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Kovacs, Eva, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Kreider, Stanley D., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Kreisberg, Robert, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - Kunin, Arthur, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Kupfer, Sherman, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Kurtzman, Neil, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - Ladimer, Irving, 1977, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Langmuir, Susan, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - Lanoue, Susan, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - Lash, Terry, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - Lasker, Lorraine, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - Lasky, Julian J., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - Lassen, Henry, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - Lavan, Spencer, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - Lavietes, Paul H., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - Leaffer, Thelma, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 407-408)
  - Lee, Philip, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - Lefebvre, Yvonne, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - Lele, R. D., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - Leonard, Carol, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - Leonard, Martha, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Leonardo da Vinci Society, Undated (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - LeQuire, Virgil S., 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - Levin, Jack, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - Levin, Murray, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Levine, Macy, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Levy, Norman, Undated (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Levy, Rona, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Lichtenstein, Lawrence M., 1967, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - Lichtman, Herbert, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - Lidov, Mika, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - Lietar, Carol, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - Lin, Tsung-Min, Undated (Box 4, Folder 425)
  - Linton, S., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 426)
  - Lipman, Arthur, 1974, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 427)
  - Lippard, Vernon W., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 428)
  - Lipsett, Mortimer, 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 429)